yuppflix.com 2016-06-17

# YUPPTV Privacy Policy

1\. PRIVACY POLICY

By using the YuppTV USA Inc., our website, the User consents to the collection, use, and storage of User information by YuppTV in the manner described in this Privacy Policy and elsewhere on the YuppTV sites. This Privacy Policy applies only to information YuppTV and the Services collects about the User and does not apply to information about the User collected by YuppTV’s affiliated providers or third party websites and offerings linked to or otherwise accessible from the YuppTV website or the Services. The information collected or received by YuppTV’s affiliated providers and/ or third parties are subject to their own privacy policies.

This Privacy Policy details important information regarding the use and disclosure of User information collected on the YuppTV USA Inc., sites to enable the User to make an informed decision about whether to use or continue using the YuppTV USA Inc., sites and the Services. It is clarified that any video, image, or other User Content posted at the direction of the User onto the YuppTV site and the Services becomes published content and shall not be considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Policy.

2\. COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

The information gathered by YuppTV may either be information that the User voluntarily supplies to YuppTV or when the information gathered on usage patterns and preferences as the User navigates through YuppTV’s sites and/ or uses the Services. An agent or affiliate of YuppTV may, at times and on being so authorized, collect information on behalf of YuppTV. Third party providers featured on or linked to by the YuppTV sites, such as vendors of products and services offered through the sites, may be gathering the same kinds of information.

Any personal information or video content that the User voluntarily discloses online (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. The Users account name (not the email address) is displayed to other Users when any videos are uploaded or messages are sent through the Services and other Users can contact the User through messages and comments. Any videos that the User submits to the YuppTV sites may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public.

Cookies. To enable YuppTV to make its sites more responsive to the needs of the Users, YuppTV may use a standard feature of browser software called a "cookie," to assign each visitor a unique, random number, a type of user ID that may reside on the Users computer. The cookie doesn't actually identify the User but identifies only the computer that is used to access the site. Advertisers and other third parties that provide products or services through the YuppTV site may also assign their own cookies to the Users browser and such process is beyond YuppTV’s control. YuppTV may use both session cookies (which are temporary and disappear after the User closes the browser) and persistent cookies (which remain after the User closes the browser and which may be used by the Users browser on subsequent visits to the site). The User may reset the web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the YuppTV sites may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.

Other Methods. The YuppTV web pages may contain electronic images (called "single-pixel GIFs" or "web beacons") that allow YuppTV and its affiliates to count users who have visited particular pages or to access certain cookies. These tools and other technologies to may be used to recognize which pages users visit, and which links they click on. These features may also be included in email newsletters so that YuppTV may learn which messages have been opened and acted upon. These tools may also enable YuppTV to verify online purchases by the User from the YuppTV sites or from third party sites that have agreed to share such information with YuppTV.

Browser Level Information and IP Addresses. The YuppTV web servers automatically collect limited information about the Users computer configuration, including browser software, the operating system, the website that referred the User, and the Users Internet Protocol (IP) address browser language, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, the order of those pages, and the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of the Users request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify the Users browser.

Third Party. YuppTV may permit third-party ad servers or ad networks, to display advertisements within the YuppTV sites. Such third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to the Users your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on YuppTV sites and automatically receive the Users IP address when this happens. The third party may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content the User sees. The User should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. YuppTV’s privacy policy does not apply to, and YuppTV cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

3\. STORAGE OF INFORMATION

Any information provided by the User to YuppTV shall be stored and held under generally accepted standards of technology and operational security in order to protect the Users personally identifiable information from loss, misuse, alteration, or destruction. Only authorized personnel are permitted access to the User information and these personnel are required to treat this information as confidential. Despite these precautions, YuppTV cannot guarantee that any and all unauthorized access to the Users information will be prevented.

All classifieds, User Content, postings, etc. are stored in the YuppTV database, even after "deletion," and may be archived elsewhere and the web logs and other records are stored indefinitely. Search engines and other sites not affiliated with YuppTV - including archive.org, google.com, etc. may archive or otherwise make available YuppTV postings.

4\. USAGE OF INFORMATION

YuppTV uses IP address information for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes. This information is also used to deliver web pages to the User upon request; to tailor the site to the interests of the users and to measure traffic within the YuppTV site.

Any personally identifiable information provided by the User is used to operate, maintain, and provide the User with the features and functionality of the YuppTV sites.

YuppTV does not use the Users email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without the Users consent except as part of a program or feature for which the User may exercise an option to not receive such messages. YuppTV may, however, use the Users email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes.

YuppTV may use both personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information to improve the quality and design of the Services and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing User preferences and trends.

YuppTV uses cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to: remember information so that the User is not required to re-enter it during subsequent visits; provide custom and personalized content and information; monitor the effectiveness of marketing campaigns; monitor logs such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and to track entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests of the User.

5\. DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

Affiliates. YuppTV may share certain types of information such as account information, diagnostic information, transaction information, and usage information with subsidiaries, affiliated companies, or other businesses or persons for the purpose of processing such information on its behalf. YuppTV requires such affiliates to process such information in compliance with this Privacy Policy and shall undertake all reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information and to use other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

Third Parties: YuppTV does not share the Users personally identifiable information with third-party companies or organizations for their commercial or marketing use without the Users express consent except as part of a specific program or feature for which the User has the ability to opt-in or opt-out. YuppTV may share non-personally-identifiable information with interested third-parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on the YuppTV sites and the Services. YuppTV may use the information to present offers to the User on behalf of business partners and advertisers. These business partners and advertisers may receive aggregate data about groups of YuppTV but do not receive information that personally identifies the User.

Transactions/Requests with Third Parties. The User may choose to use the Services to purchase goods/services from third party providers. YuppTV may share necessary information with third parties to fulfil a transaction the User has requested. YuppTV may share information where the User has consented to the sharing of such information, or except as described in this Privacy Policy.

Legal Obligations/Fraud. YuppTV may be required to may disclose such records as it believes in good faith to be appropriate or necessary to protect its legitimate business interests, safeguard others, or respond to legal process like subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process, or to establish or exercise its legal rights or defend against legal claims. The information may also be required to be disclosed in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of TOU, or as otherwise required or permitted by law.

Statistical Information. Much of the information YuppTV collects is in the form of aggregated statistics, such as the traffic that visits various pages within the Services, the habits and preferences of the audience, etc. Such aggregated information does not include any personally identifiable information and YuppTV may use such aggregated information and/ or disclose it to third parties as it deems fit.

6\. SECURITY OF INFORMATION

YuppTV has established safeguards to help prevent unauthorized access to or misuse of User information, but cannot guarantee that such information will never be disclosed in a manner inconsistent with this Privacy Policy. To protect the Users privacy and security, YuppTV may use passwords to help verify the Users identity before granting access or making corrections to any User information.

YuppTV uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of User information. YuppTV, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to YuppTV by the User and is transmitted at the Users own risk. Once YuppTV receives the transmission of information, YuppTV makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of its systems. However, YuppTV cannot a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

If YuppTV becomes aware of a security systems breach, then YuppTV may attempt to notify the User electronically so that the User can take appropriate protective steps or may post a notice on the YuppTV sites. Depending on where the User resides, the User may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw consent from receiving electronic notice) the User should notify YuppTV using the contact form.

7\. USER CHOICES

The User may decline to submit personally identifiable information through the YuppTV sites, in which case YuppTV may not be able to provide certain services. If the User opts to register with and provide information to YuppTV, the User will have the opportunity to unsubscribe, review, update, or delete the information provided at any time. If the User opts to remove registration information completely, the User may not be able to continue using certain services that require registration.

To protect the Users privacy and security, YuppTV takes reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to verify the Users identity before granting profile access or making corrections. The User is responsible for maintaining the secrecy of the unique password and account information at all times. It is clarified that media files uploaded by Users to the YuppTV sites and the Services cannot be removed and remain subject to the TOU.

The User may contact YuppTV with any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, personal information, User consent, or opt-in or opt-out choices using the contact form.

8\. CHILDRENS PRIVACY

YuppTV websites are not intentionally designed for or directed at persons less than 18 years of age. YuppTV does not knowingly permit any person who is under 18 years of age to register with the Services or to provide any other personally identifying information. Any person under 18 years of age visiting the YuppTV sites is prohibited from accessing or using the Services in any manner and at any time. If YuppTV becomes aware that any personally identifiable information of persons less than 18 years of age has been collected on the YuppTV sites without verified parental consent, then YuppTV will take the appropriate steps to delete any such information.

9\. CHANGE IN CONTROL

In the event that YuppTV is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, YuppTV reserves the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information collected from the Users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the event of bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, YuppTV may not be able to control how the your personal information is treated, transferred, or used.

10\. MODIFICATIONS

YuppTV may update or revise this Privacy Policy from time to time and the User is advised to review this Policy periodically. Any significant changes to YuppTV ‘S information practices will be intimated to the User with appropriate online notice. The Users continued use of the YuppTV sites constitutes the Users agreement to this Privacy Policy and any future modifications/revisions.

11\. CONTACT INFORMATION

Users may contact YuppTV with any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy using the contact form or may address such queries and / or comments to info@YuppTV.com
